# **James Ahn**

portfolio / jamesahn.co

ux/ui designer jamesahn0717@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/james-ahn (236)-512-9610

Summary of Skills

UX Design	HTML	Photoshop	Teamwork
UI Design	CSS	Illustrator	Problem Solving
Prototyping	Python	Premiere Pro	Time Management
Figma	InDesign	Lightroom	Balsamiq

1 year + of key experience in the travel industry, combined with a solid academic background specializing in user experience

2 years + of prototyping and design sprints for quick ideas

3 years + of working in Figma with teammates and efficiently got work done with them in an effective pace

# **Experience**

### **Business and Design Mentor** - Starterhacks at University of Waterloo

Jan 2020

Mentored students participating in StarterHacks (Canada's largest

beginner-focused hackathon) with potential routes and tactics on executing with a balanced business model

Used advantage of my dual background in business and design to apply real world concepts to fledgling projects that needed fleshing out

#### **UX/UI Design Intern** - Tugolo

May 2019 - August 2019

Re-designed Tugolo's entire web interface using Figma to make the user-end experience more interactive and accessible

Took control of the mobile platform design, a key part of the company's target group, while working in a 5-person team of one other designer and three developers

Implemented wireframes and high-fidelity models, compiling user feedback and testing closely with other employees

#### **UX/UI Designer** - Tastebuds

Jan 2020 - present

Leading the design responsibility for a start-up, making adjustments on the current interface to present a more simple and intuitive look

Highly involved in designing the user's profile and statistics of their progress with and motivated by user feedback

# **Education**

# Honours Global Business and Digital Arts — University of Waterloo

Sept 2017 - April 2021

**Exchange Program** - Singapore University of Technology and Design

Sept 2019 - Dec 2019

# Activities & Interests

Snowboarding Camping Hiking Travelling

Photography Videography

#### **Snowboarding**

Participated in the snowboarding club in my high school and went to provincials and won 3rd place boys snowboarding and 1st place in mixed snowboarding

#### **Travelling**

Went on exchange to Singapore and travelled to 5 different countries, adding count to the 21 countries I've travelled to

Continuously expanding my knowledge through experiencing different cultures